[[{"question": "What episode is The Empire Strikes Back?", "correct_answer": 5, "incorrect_answers": [2, 4, 1]}, {"question": "How tall is C-3PO?", "correct_answer": "167", "incorrect_answers": ["97", "202", "165"]}, {"question": "What is the average height of a Trandoshan?", "correct_answer": "200", "incorrect_answers": ["66", "n/a", "100"]}, {"question": "What language does a Droid speak?", "correct_answer": "n/a", "incorrect_answers": ["Galactic basic", "Huttese", "Sullutese"]}, {"question": "What is Alderaan's terrain like?", "correct_answer": "grasslands, mountains", "incorrect_answers": ["gas giant", "grassy hills, swamps, forests, mountains", "tundra, ice caves, mountain ranges"]}], [{"question": "When did episode 2 come out?", "correct_answer": "2002-05-16", "incorrect_answers": ["1980-05-17", "1977-05-25", "1999-05-19"]}, {"question": "What's the population of Alderaan?", "correct_answer": "2000000000", "incorrect_answers": ["4500000000", "unknown", "1000000000000"]}, {"question": "When was Owen Lars born?", "correct_answer": "52BBY", "incorrect_answers": ["24BBY", "57BBY", "112BBY"]}, {"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a Storm IV Twin-Pod cloud car?", "correct_answer": "10", "incorrect_answers": ["50", "50000", "2000000"]}, {"question": "What is the average height of a Human?", "correct_answer": "180", "incorrect_answers": ["180", "300", "200"]}], [{"question": "What episode is Revenge of the Sith?", "correct_answer": 3, "incorrect_answers": [4, 6, 2]}, {"question": "Who makes the Y-wing?", "correct_answer": "Koensayr Manufacturing", "incorrect_answers": ["Kuat Drive Yards", "Imperial Department of Military Research, Sienar Fleet Systems", "Corellian Engineering Corporation"]}, {"question": "What is Coruscant's terrain like?", "correct_answer": "cityscape, mountains", "incorrect_answers": ["swamp, jungles", "grassy hills, swamps, forests, mountains", "tundra, ice caves, mountain ranges"]}, {"question": "How much does the Sand Crawler cost?", "correct_answer": "150000", "incorrect_answers": ["unknown", "75000", "unknown"]}, {"question": "When was R5-D4 born?", "correct_answer": "unknown", "incorrect_answers": ["52BBY", "19BBY", "19BBY"]}], [{"question": "What is the average lifespan of a Mon Calamari?", "correct_answer": "unknown", "incorrect_answers": ["unknown", "indefinite", "unknown"]}, {"question": "How much does the Sail barge cost?", "correct_answer": "285000", "incorrect_answers": ["14500", "10550", "unknown"]}, {"question": "How heavy is Leia Organa?", "correct_answer": "49", "incorrect_answers": ["136", "84", "32"]}, {"question": "How much does the Y-wing cost?", "correct_answer": "134999", "incorrect_answers": ["100000", "240000", "unknown"]}, {"question": "How tall is Obi-Wan Kenobi?", "correct_answer": "182", "incorrect_answers": ["183", "96", "172"]}], [{"question": "Who makes the TIE bomber?", "correct_answer": "Sienar Fleet Systems", "incorrect_answers": ["Kuat Drive Yards, Imperial Department of Military Research", "SoroSuub Corporation", "Corellia Mining Corporation"]}, {"question": "How tall is R2-D2?", "correct_answer": "96", "incorrect_answers": ["178", "150", "167"]}, {"question": "How much does the Executor cost?", "correct_answer": "1143350000", "incorrect_answers": ["134999", "100000", "unknown"]}, {"question": "What's the diameter of Hoth?", "correct_answer": "7200", "incorrect_answers": ["10465", "10200", "19720"]}, {"question": "What episode is Attack of the Clones?", "correct_answer": 2, "incorrect_answers": [1, 4, 6]}], [{"question": "Who makes the AT-AT?", "correct_answer": "Kuat Drive Yards, Imperial Department of Military Research", "incorrect_answers": ["Sienar Fleet Systems", "SoroSuub Corporation", "Incom Corporation"]}, {"question": "What is Endor's terrain like?", "correct_answer": "forests, mountains, lakes", "incorrect_answers": ["tundra, ice caves, mountain ranges", "grasslands, mountains", "grassy hills, swamps, forests, mountains"]}, {"question": "Who makes the Y-wing?", "correct_answer": "Koensayr Manufacturing", "incorrect_answers": ["Corellian Engineering Corporation", "Kuat Drive Yards", "Gallofree Yards, Inc."]}, {"question": "How tall is R5-D4?", "correct_answer": "97", "incorrect_answers": ["182", "165", "172"]}, {"question": "What is the average height of a Wookie?", "correct_answer": "210", "incorrect_answers": ["180", "160", "66"]}], [{"question": "How much does the Sail barge cost?", "correct_answer": "285000", "incorrect_answers": ["150000", "unknown", "unknown"]}, {"question": "What is the average height of a Sullustan?", "correct_answer": "180", "incorrect_answers": ["180", "66", "n/a"]}, {"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a Y-wing?", "correct_answer": "110", "incorrect_answers": ["250000000", "110", "1000000000000"]}, {"question": "How tall is Owen Lars?", "correct_answer": "178", "incorrect_answers": ["150", "202", "182"]}, {"question": "When did episode 1 come out?", "correct_answer": "1999-05-19", "incorrect_answers": ["1977-05-25", "1983-05-25", "2002-05-16"]}], [{"question": "How much does the TIE/LN starfighter cost?", "correct_answer": "unknown", "incorrect_answers": ["75000", "unknown", "unknown"]}, {"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a Sentinel-class landing craft?", "correct_answer": "180000", "incorrect_answers": ["36000000", "1000000000000", "250000000"]}, {"question": "What's the population of Kamino?", "correct_answer": "1000000000", "incorrect_answers": ["1000", "4500000000", "unknown"]}, {"question": "What's the diameter of Tatooine?", "correct_answer": "10465", "incorrect_answers": ["12500", "8900", "12240"]}, {"question": "How heavy is Beru Whitesun lars?", "correct_answer": "75", "incorrect_answers": ["84", "32", "77"]}], [{"question": "Who makes the CR90 corvette?", "correct_answer": "Corellian Engineering Corporation", "incorrect_answers": ["Corellian Engineering Corporation", "Sienar Fleet Systems, Cyngus Spaceworks", "Incom Corporation"]}, {"question": "What language does a Wookie speak?", "correct_answer": "Shyriiwook", "incorrect_answers": ["Mon Calamarian", "Dosh", "Ewokese"]}, {"question": "What's the population of Kamino?", "correct_answer": "1000000000", "incorrect_answers": ["1000000000000", "1000", "30000000"]}, {"question": "Who makes the AT-AT?", "correct_answer": "Kuat Drive Yards, Imperial Department of Military Research", "incorrect_answers": ["Sienar Fleet Systems", "Sienar Fleet Systems", "Bespin Motors"]}, {"question": "What is Tatooine's terrain like?", "correct_answer": "desert", "incorrect_answers": ["jungle, rainforests", "grasslands, mountains", "gas giant"]}], [{"question": "What is Alderaan's terrain like?", "correct_answer": "grasslands, mountains", "incorrect_answers": ["grassy hills, swamps, forests, mountains", "desert", "gas giant"]}, {"question": "How heavy is R2-D2?", "correct_answer": "32", "incorrect_answers": ["77", "49", "32"]}, {"question": "Who makes the Y-wing?", "correct_answer": "Koensayr Manufacturing", "incorrect_answers": ["Incom Corporation", "Kuat Drive Yards, Fondor Shipyards", "Imperial Department of Military Research, Sienar Fleet Systems"]}, {"question": "What's the population of Hoth?", "correct_answer": "unknown", "incorrect_answers": ["1000", "1000000000000", "unknown"]}, {"question": "What is the average lifespan of a Yoda's species?", "correct_answer": "900", "incorrect_answers": ["unknown", "unknown", "unknown"]}], [{"question": "What episode is The Phantom Menace?", "correct_answer": 1, "incorrect_answers": [2, 5, 4]}, {"question": "When was Obi-Wan Kenobi born?", "correct_answer": "57BBY", "incorrect_answers": ["52BBY", "47BBY", "19BBY"]}, {"question": "What is Dagobah's terrain like?", "correct_answer": "swamp, jungles", "incorrect_answers": ["tundra, ice caves, mountain ranges", "jungle, rainforests", "desert"]}, {"question": "When did episode 3 come out?", "correct_answer": "2005-05-19", "incorrect_answers": ["1983-05-25", "1977-05-25", "1980-05-17"]}, {"question": "What language does a Hutt speak?", "correct_answer": "Huttese", "incorrect_answers": ["Galactic basic", "Shyriiwook", "Galactic Basic"]}], [{"question": "Who makes the AT-AT?", "correct_answer": "Kuat Drive Yards, Imperial Department of Military Research", "incorrect_answers": ["Bespin Motors", "Sienar Fleet Systems", "SoroSuub Corporation"]}, {"question": "How much does the X-wing cost?", "correct_answer": "149999", "incorrect_answers": ["unknown", "1000000000000", "1143350000"]}, {"question": "What episode is Attack of the Clones?", "correct_answer": 2, "incorrect_answers": [1, 5, 6]}, {"question": "How heavy is R2-D2?", "correct_answer": "32", "incorrect_answers": ["77", "32", "75"]}, {"question": "What's the population of Endor?", "correct_answer": "30000000", "incorrect_answers": ["unknown", "1000000000000", "200000"]}], [{"question": "What is the average lifespan of a Droid?", "correct_answer": "indefinite", "incorrect_answers": ["unknown", "unknown", "400"]}, {"question": "What is the average height of a Rodian?", "correct_answer": "170", "incorrect_answers": ["200", "100", "180"]}, {"question": "What's the diameter of Bespin?", "correct_answer": "118000", "incorrect_answers": ["7200", "19720", "8900"]}, {"question": "How much does the X-34 landspeeder cost?", "correct_answer": "10550", "incorrect_answers": ["unknown", "unknown", "14500"]}, {"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a Storm IV Twin-Pod cloud car?", "correct_answer": "10", "incorrect_answers": ["65", "50", "1000"]}], [{"question": "When was Darth Vader born?", "correct_answer": "41.9BBY", "incorrect_answers": ["unknown", "57BBY", "24BBY"]}, {"question": "How much does the TIE bomber cost?", "correct_answer": "unknown", "incorrect_answers": ["unknown", "10550", "14500"]}, {"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a TIE Advanced x1?", "correct_answer": "150", "incorrect_answers": ["110", "180000", "100000"]}, {"question": "What language does a Sullustan speak?", "correct_answer": "Sullutese", "incorrect_answers": ["Mon Calamarian", "n/a", "Galatic Basic"]}, {"question": "What episode is A New Hope?", "correct_answer": 4, "incorrect_answers": [3, 5, 1]}], [{"question": "What language does a Yoda's species speak?", "correct_answer": "Galactic basic", "incorrect_answers": ["n/a", "Shyriiwook", "Galatic Basic"]}, {"question": "How much does the Storm IV Twin-Pod cloud car cost?", "correct_answer": "75000", "incorrect_answers": ["14500", "unknown", "unknown"]}, {"question": "Who makes the X-wing?", "correct_answer": "Incom Corporation", "incorrect_answers": ["Kuat Drive Yards", "Sienar Fleet Systems", "Koensayr Manufacturing"]}, {"question": "How heavy is Owen Lars?", "correct_answer": "120", "incorrect_answers": ["136", "32", "77"]}, {"question": "How tall is Beru Whitesun lars?", "correct_answer": "165", "incorrect_answers": ["172", "202", "167"]}], [{"question": "What is the average lifespan of a Mon Calamari?", "correct_answer": "unknown", "incorrect_answers": ["120", "unknown", "indefinite"]}, {"question": "Who makes the Star Destroyer?", "correct_answer": "Kuat Drive Yards", "incorrect_answers": ["Sienar Fleet Systems", "Sienar Fleet Systems, Cyngus Spaceworks", "Corellian Engineering Corporation"]}, {"question": "What is the average height of a Hutt?", "correct_answer": "300", "incorrect_answers": ["66", "n/a", "100"]}, {"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a Snowspeeder?", "correct_answer": "10", "incorrect_answers": ["2000000", "200", "65"]}, {"question": "What language does a Yoda's species speak?", "correct_answer": "Galactic basic", "incorrect_answers": ["Shyriiwook", "Galatic Basic", "Ewokese"]}], [{"question": "How tall is Obi-Wan Kenobi?", "correct_answer": "182", "incorrect_answers": ["165", "202", "178"]}, {"question": "What is the average height of a Trandoshan?", "correct_answer": "200", "incorrect_answers": ["170", "160", "n/a"]}, {"question": "How heavy is R2-D2?", "correct_answer": "32", "incorrect_answers": ["77", "75", "49"]}, {"question": "When was Darth Vader born?", "correct_answer": "41.9BBY", "incorrect_answers": ["52BBY", "47BBY", "19BBY"]}, {"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a Rebel transport?", "correct_answer": "19000000", "incorrect_answers": ["110", "110", "1000000000000"]}], [{"question": "How tall is Beru Whitesun lars?", "correct_answer": "165", "incorrect_answers": ["150", "178", "182"]}, {"question": "When did episode 2 come out?", "correct_answer": "2002-05-16", "incorrect_answers": ["1983-05-25", "1999-05-19", "1977-05-25"]}, {"question": "How much does the AT-ST cost?", "correct_answer": "unknown", "incorrect_answers": ["unknown", "75000", "unknown"]}, {"question": "What language does a Ewok speak?", "correct_answer": "Ewokese", "incorrect_answers": ["Sullutese", "Galatic Basic", "Galactic basic"]}, {"question": "Who makes the X-34 landspeeder?", "correct_answer": "SoroSuub Corporation", "incorrect_answers": ["Incom Corporation", "Bespin Motors", "Corellia Mining Corporation"]}], [{"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a Rebel transport?", "correct_answer": "19000000", "incorrect_answers": ["150", "100000", "110"]}, {"question": "What is the average lifespan of a Rodian?", "correct_answer": "unknown", "incorrect_answers": ["400", "900", "unknown"]}, {"question": "What language does a Trandoshan speak?", "correct_answer": "Dosh", "incorrect_answers": ["Ewokese", "Galactic Basic", "Huttese"]}, {"question": "When was Leia Organa born?", "correct_answer": "19BBY", "incorrect_answers": ["24BBY", "19BBY", "unknown"]}, {"question": "Who makes the TIE bomber?", "correct_answer": "Sienar Fleet Systems", "incorrect_answers": ["Kuat Drive Yards, Imperial Department of Military Research", "Incom Corporation", "Ubrikkian Industries Custom Vehicle Division"]}], [{"question": "What language does a Trandoshan speak?", "correct_answer": "Dosh", "incorrect_answers": ["Sullutese", "Galatic Basic", "Galactic Basic"]}, {"question": "What is the average lifespan of a Wookie?", "correct_answer": "400", "incorrect_answers": ["unknown", "unknown", "unknown"]}, {"question": "How tall is R2-D2?", "correct_answer": "96", "incorrect_answers": ["165", "167", "202"]}, {"question": "What is Dagobah's terrain like?", "correct_answer": "swamp, jungles", "incorrect_answers": ["tundra, ice caves, mountain ranges", "grassy hills, swamps, forests, mountains", "cityscape, mountains"]}, {"question": "What's the population of Kamino?", "correct_answer": "1000000000", "incorrect_answers": ["1000", "30000000", "6000000"]}], [{"question": "What is Bespin's terrain like?", "correct_answer": "gas giant", "incorrect_answers": ["tundra, ice caves, mountain ranges", "grassy hills, swamps, forests, mountains", "desert"]}, {"question": "How much does the Death Star cost?", "correct_answer": "1000000000000", "incorrect_answers": ["1143350000", "150000000", "240000"]}, {"question": "How heavy is R2-D2?", "correct_answer": "32", "incorrect_answers": ["75", "49", "77"]}, {"question": "When was Luke Skywalker born?", "correct_answer": "19BBY", "incorrect_answers": ["47BBY", "24BBY", "41.9BBY"]}, {"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a X-wing?", "correct_answer": "110", "incorrect_answers": ["150", "36000000", "180000"]}], [{"question": "Who makes the Sand Crawler?", "correct_answer": "Corellia Mining Corporation", "incorrect_answers": ["Incom corporation", "Kuat Drive Yards, Imperial Department of Military Research", "Sienar Fleet Systems"]}, {"question": "What is the average height of a Droid?", "correct_answer": "n/a", "incorrect_answers": ["66", "210", "180"]}, {"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a Y-wing?", "correct_answer": "110", "incorrect_answers": ["1000000000000", "100000", "19000000"]}, {"question": "Who makes the Executor?", "correct_answer": "Kuat Drive Yards, Fondor Shipyards", "incorrect_answers": ["Gallofree Yards, Inc.", "Sienar Fleet Systems", "Corellian Engineering Corporation"]}, {"question": "When did episode 2 come out?", "correct_answer": "2002-05-16", "incorrect_answers": ["1977-05-25", "1980-05-17", "1999-05-19"]}], [{"question": "What's the population of Alderaan?", "correct_answer": "2000000000", "incorrect_answers": ["6000000", "200000", "unknown"]}, {"question": "What is the average lifespan of a Rodian?", "correct_answer": "unknown", "incorrect_answers": ["400", "unknown", "unknown"]}, {"question": "Who makes the Y-wing?", "correct_answer": "Koensayr Manufacturing", "incorrect_answers": ["Sienar Fleet Systems, Cyngus Spaceworks", "Kuat Drive Yards, Fondor Shipyards", "Corellian Engineering Corporation"]}, {"question": "What is the average height of a Human?", "correct_answer": "180", "incorrect_answers": ["160", "300", "100"]}, {"question": "How heavy is Luke Skywalker?", "correct_answer": "77", "incorrect_answers": ["120", "49", "32"]}], [{"question": "How much does the AT-AT cost?", "correct_answer": "unknown", "incorrect_answers": ["10550", "75000", "285000"]}, {"question": "What is Kamino's terrain like?", "correct_answer": "ocean", "incorrect_answers": ["gas giant", "cityscape, mountains", "swamp, jungles"]}, {"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a CR90 corvette?", "correct_answer": "3000000", "incorrect_answers": ["150", "19000000", "110"]}, {"question": "Who makes the Death Star?", "correct_answer": "Imperial Department of Military Research, Sienar Fleet Systems", "incorrect_answers": ["Kuat Drive Yards", "Corellian Engineering Corporation", "Corellian Engineering Corporation"]}, {"question": "What's the population of Endor?", "correct_answer": "30000000", "incorrect_answers": ["6000000", "unknown", "1000"]}], [{"question": "Who makes the T-16 skyhopper?", "correct_answer": "Incom Corporation", "incorrect_answers": ["SoroSuub Corporation", "Corellia Mining Corporation", "Kuat Drive Yards, Imperial Department of Military Research"]}, {"question": "How heavy is Leia Organa?", "correct_answer": "49", "incorrect_answers": ["136", "120", "32"]}, {"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a Executor?", "correct_answer": "250000000", "incorrect_answers": ["3000000", "36000000", "1000000000000"]}, {"question": "How much does the TIE/LN starfighter cost?", "correct_answer": "unknown", "incorrect_answers": ["285000", "unknown", "75000"]}, {"question": "What episode is The Empire Strikes Back?", "correct_answer": 5, "incorrect_answers": [1, 3, 2]}], [{"question": "When was Leia Organa born?", "correct_answer": "19BBY", "incorrect_answers": ["24BBY", "33BBY", "unknown"]}, {"question": "What is the average height of a Human?", "correct_answer": "180", "incorrect_answers": ["210", "n/a", "100"]}, {"question": "How much does the X-34 landspeeder cost?", "correct_answer": "10550", "incorrect_answers": ["285000", "unknown", "14500"]}, {"question": "What is the average lifespan of a Rodian?", "correct_answer": "unknown", "incorrect_answers": ["unknown", "indefinite", "unknown"]}, {"question": "What is Dagobah's terrain like?", "correct_answer": "swamp, jungles", "incorrect_answers": ["jungle, rainforests", "tundra, ice caves, mountain ranges", "forests, mountains, lakes"]}], [{"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a Storm IV Twin-Pod cloud car?", "correct_answer": "10", "incorrect_answers": ["1000", "200", "50000"]}, {"question": "What episode is The Empire Strikes Back?", "correct_answer": 5, "incorrect_answers": [3, 1, 4]}, {"question": "How tall is Beru Whitesun lars?", "correct_answer": "165", "incorrect_answers": ["202", "178", "172"]}, {"question": "What is Yavin IV's terrain like?", "correct_answer": "jungle, rainforests", "incorrect_answers": ["grassy hills, swamps, forests, mountains", "desert", "cityscape, mountains"]}, {"question": "What's the population of Bespin?", "correct_answer": "6000000", "incorrect_answers": ["4500000000", "unknown", "1000000000"]}], [{"question": "What language does a Ewok speak?", "correct_answer": "Ewokese", "incorrect_answers": ["Dosh", "Mon Calamarian", "Galactic basic"]}, {"question": "How much does the Storm IV Twin-Pod cloud car cost?", "correct_answer": "75000", "incorrect_answers": ["285000", "unknown", "10550"]}, {"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a Sentinel-class landing craft?", "correct_answer": "180000", "incorrect_answers": ["100000", "250000000", "150"]}, {"question": "When was R2-D2 born?", "correct_answer": "33BBY", "incorrect_answers": ["19BBY", "52BBY", "24BBY"]}, {"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a TIE bomber?", "correct_answer": "none", "incorrect_answers": ["200", "1000", "50000"]}], [{"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a TIE/LN starfighter?", "correct_answer": "65", "incorrect_answers": ["none", "50", "2000000"]}, {"question": "How much does the Sand Crawler cost?", "correct_answer": "150000", "incorrect_answers": ["10550", "unknown", "unknown"]}, {"question": "What is the average lifespan of a Trandoshan?", "correct_answer": "unknown", "incorrect_answers": ["unknown", "unknown", "unknown"]}, {"question": "How heavy is Owen Lars?", "correct_answer": "120", "incorrect_answers": ["136", "75", "75"]}, {"question": "What's the population of Tatooine?", "correct_answer": "200000", "incorrect_answers": ["4500000000", "1000000000", "2000000000"]}], [{"question": "What is the average lifespan of a Trandoshan?", "correct_answer": "unknown", "incorrect_answers": ["unknown", "unknown", "400"]}, {"question": "How tall is C-3PO?", "correct_answer": "167", "incorrect_answers": ["97", "96", "183"]}, {"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a Y-wing?", "correct_answer": "110", "incorrect_answers": ["1000000000000", "36000000", "19000000"]}, {"question": "What's the diameter of Kamino?", "correct_answer": "19720", "incorrect_answers": ["4900", "7200", "10465"]}, {"question": "How much does the Millennium Falcon cost?", "correct_answer": "100000", "incorrect_answers": ["149999", "240000", "134999"]}], [{"question": "Who makes the Star Destroyer?", "correct_answer": "Kuat Drive Yards", "incorrect_answers": ["Sienar Fleet Systems", "Imperial Department of Military Research, Sienar Fleet Systems", "Kuat Drive Yards, Fondor Shipyards"]}, {"question": "What language does a Rodian speak?", "correct_answer": "Galatic Basic", "incorrect_answers": ["Shyriiwook", "Mon Calamarian", "Galactic Basic"]}, {"question": "What's the diameter of Naboo?", "correct_answer": "12120", "incorrect_answers": ["12500", "118000", "8900"]}, {"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a Snowspeeder?", "correct_answer": "10", "incorrect_answers": ["50", "1000", "none"]}, {"question": "What is the average height of a Sullustan?", "correct_answer": "180", "incorrect_answers": ["n/a", "210", "66"]}], [{"question": "Who makes the Millennium Falcon?", "correct_answer": "Corellian Engineering Corporation", "incorrect_answers": ["Sienar Fleet Systems", "Gallofree Yards, Inc.", "Sienar Fleet Systems, Cyngus Spaceworks"]}, {"question": "What is Tatooine's terrain like?", "correct_answer": "desert", "incorrect_answers": ["grasslands, mountains", "forests, mountains, lakes", "swamp, jungles"]}, {"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a Executor?", "correct_answer": "250000000", "incorrect_answers": ["180000", "1000000000000", "3000000"]}, {"question": "When was C-3PO born?", "correct_answer": "112BBY", "incorrect_answers": ["19BBY", "24BBY", "41.9BBY"]}, {"question": "What is the average height of a Droid?", "correct_answer": "n/a", "incorrect_answers": ["200", "66", "300"]}], [{"question": "What's the population of Hoth?", "correct_answer": "unknown", "incorrect_answers": ["1000", "30000000", "2000000000"]}, {"question": "What is the average height of a Trandoshan?", "correct_answer": "200", "incorrect_answers": ["66", "180", "180"]}, {"question": "How tall is C-3PO?", "correct_answer": "167", "incorrect_answers": ["183", "172", "165"]}, {"question": "What episode is Return of the Jedi?", "correct_answer": 6, "incorrect_answers": [4, 2, 1]}, {"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a Storm IV Twin-Pod cloud car?", "correct_answer": "10", "incorrect_answers": ["none", "10", "5"]}], [{"question": "What's the diameter of Tatooine?", "correct_answer": "10465", "incorrect_answers": ["7200", "10200", "118000"]}, {"question": "When was Obi-Wan Kenobi born?", "correct_answer": "57BBY", "incorrect_answers": ["33BBY", "unknown", "19BBY"]}, {"question": "Who makes the TIE Advanced x1?", "correct_answer": "Sienar Fleet Systems", "incorrect_answers": ["Imperial Department of Military Research, Sienar Fleet Systems", "Koensayr Manufacturing", "Corellian Engineering Corporation"]}, {"question": "How much does the AT-ST cost?", "correct_answer": "unknown", "incorrect_answers": ["unknown", "unknown", "unknown"]}, {"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a Sail barge?", "correct_answer": "2000000", "incorrect_answers": ["5", "50000", "10"]}], [{"question": "When was C-3PO born?", "correct_answer": "112BBY", "incorrect_answers": ["33BBY", "52BBY", "24BBY"]}, {"question": "What's the population of Dagobah?", "correct_answer": "unknown", "incorrect_answers": ["unknown", "6000000", "1000"]}, {"question": "Who makes the Rebel transport?", "correct_answer": "Gallofree Yards, Inc.", "incorrect_answers": ["Sienar Fleet Systems, Cyngus Spaceworks", "Incom Corporation", "Imperial Department of Military Research, Sienar Fleet Systems"]}, {"question": "How much does the Star Destroyer cost?", "correct_answer": "150000000", "incorrect_answers": ["1143350000", "100000", "unknown"]}, {"question": "What is the average lifespan of a Sullustan?", "correct_answer": "unknown", "incorrect_answers": ["1000", "900", "400"]}], [{"question": "What episode is The Phantom Menace?", "correct_answer": 1, "incorrect_answers": [4, 5, 3]}, {"question": "What is the average height of a Wookie?", "correct_answer": "210", "incorrect_answers": ["66", "100", "170"]}, {"question": "What is Hoth's terrain like?", "correct_answer": "tundra, ice caves, mountain ranges", "incorrect_answers": ["forests, mountains, lakes", "grassy hills, swamps, forests, mountains", "swamp, jungles"]}, {"question": "What's the diameter of Bespin?", "correct_answer": "118000", "incorrect_answers": ["12240", "8900", "19720"]}, {"question": "How heavy is Darth Vader?", "correct_answer": "136", "incorrect_answers": ["120", "75", "75"]}], [{"question": "What's the diameter of Endor?", "correct_answer": "4900", "incorrect_answers": ["12120", "12240", "10200"]}, {"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a Death Star?", "correct_answer": "1000000000000", "incorrect_answers": ["250000000", "150", "110"]}, {"question": "How heavy is Darth Vader?", "correct_answer": "136", "incorrect_answers": ["77", "75", "32"]}, {"question": "How much does the Y-wing cost?", "correct_answer": "134999", "incorrect_answers": ["1000000000000", "unknown", "100000"]}, {"question": "How tall is R2-D2?", "correct_answer": "96", "incorrect_answers": ["178", "150", "97"]}], [{"question": "What's the population of Alderaan?", "correct_answer": "2000000000", "incorrect_answers": ["30000000", "200000", "1000000000"]}, {"question": "What language does a Mon Calamari speak?", "correct_answer": "Mon Calamarian", "incorrect_answers": ["Galactic Basic", "Ewokese", "Sullutese"]}, {"question": "How much does the Millennium Falcon cost?", "correct_answer": "100000", "incorrect_answers": ["unknown", "240000", "149999"]}, {"question": "When did episode 6 come out?", "correct_answer": "1983-05-25", "incorrect_answers": ["2002-05-16", "1980-05-17", "1999-05-19"]}, {"question": "What's the diameter of Dagobah?", "correct_answer": "8900", "incorrect_answers": ["10200", "10465", "12240"]}], [{"question": "What's the diameter of Dagobah?", "correct_answer": "8900", "incorrect_answers": ["12120", "19720", "10465"]}, {"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a Rebel transport?", "correct_answer": "19000000", "incorrect_answers": ["250000000", "36000000", "110"]}, {"question": "What language does a Ewok speak?", "correct_answer": "Ewokese", "incorrect_answers": ["Galactic basic", "Galatic Basic", "Mon Calamarian"]}, {"question": "How heavy is C-3PO?", "correct_answer": "75", "incorrect_answers": ["32", "136", "77"]}, {"question": "How tall is Biggs Darklighter?", "correct_answer": "183", "incorrect_answers": ["97", "182", "172"]}], [{"question": "What's the diameter of Bespin?", "correct_answer": "118000", "incorrect_answers": ["10200", "8900", "10465"]}, {"question": "How tall is R5-D4?", "correct_answer": "97", "incorrect_answers": ["202", "183", "96"]}, {"question": "What is the average lifespan of a Rodian?", "correct_answer": "unknown", "incorrect_answers": ["unknown", "unknown", "120"]}, {"question": "What language does a Mon Calamari speak?", "correct_answer": "Mon Calamarian", "incorrect_answers": ["Dosh", "Galactic Basic", "Huttese"]}, {"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a TIE/LN starfighter?", "correct_answer": "65", "incorrect_answers": ["10", "50000", "5"]}], [{"question": "Who makes the X-wing?", "correct_answer": "Incom Corporation", "incorrect_answers": ["Kuat Drive Yards", "Koensayr Manufacturing", "Kuat Drive Yards, Fondor Shipyards"]}, {"question": "What episode is Attack of the Clones?", "correct_answer": 2, "incorrect_answers": [5, 3, 4]}, {"question": "What is the average height of a Sullustan?", "correct_answer": "180", "incorrect_answers": ["300", "210", "66"]}, {"question": "How tall is Darth Vader?", "correct_answer": "202", "incorrect_answers": ["178", "165", "172"]}, {"question": "How heavy is R2-D2?", "correct_answer": "32", "incorrect_answers": ["77", "49", "75"]}], [{"question": "What is the average lifespan of a Sullustan?", "correct_answer": "unknown", "incorrect_answers": ["1000", "900", "unknown"]}, {"question": "Who makes the Star Destroyer?", "correct_answer": "Kuat Drive Yards", "incorrect_answers": ["Sienar Fleet Systems", "Corellian Engineering Corporation", "Incom Corporation"]}, {"question": "What is the average height of a Wookie?", "correct_answer": "210", "incorrect_answers": ["100", "66", "300"]}, {"question": "What's the diameter of Kamino?", "correct_answer": "19720", "incorrect_answers": ["10200", "118000", "4900"]}, {"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a Storm IV Twin-Pod cloud car?", "correct_answer": "10", "incorrect_answers": ["10", "1000", "5"]}], [{"question": "When did episode 5 come out?", "correct_answer": "1980-05-17", "incorrect_answers": ["2002-05-16", "1999-05-19", "2005-05-19"]}, {"question": "What is Dagobah's terrain like?", "correct_answer": "swamp, jungles", "incorrect_answers": ["desert", "tundra, ice caves, mountain ranges", "grasslands, mountains"]}, {"question": "How heavy is Beru Whitesun lars?", "correct_answer": "75", "incorrect_answers": ["75", "136", "49"]}, {"question": "What language does a Ewok speak?", "correct_answer": "Ewokese", "incorrect_answers": ["Galatic Basic", "n/a", "Dosh"]}, {"question": "How much does the X-wing cost?", "correct_answer": "149999", "incorrect_answers": ["150000000", "unknown", "unknown"]}], [{"question": "Who makes the Sand Crawler?", "correct_answer": "Corellia Mining Corporation", "incorrect_answers": ["Sienar Fleet Systems", "Incom Corporation", "Ubrikkian Industries Custom Vehicle Division"]}, {"question": "When was C-3PO born?", "correct_answer": "112BBY", "incorrect_answers": ["41.9BBY", "57BBY", "47BBY"]}, {"question": "What language does a Yoda's species speak?", "correct_answer": "Galactic basic", "incorrect_answers": ["Dosh", "Galatic Basic", "Galactic Basic"]}, {"question": "What is the average height of a Hutt?", "correct_answer": "300", "incorrect_answers": ["160", "180", "200"]}, {"question": "How tall is Luke Skywalker?", "correct_answer": "172", "incorrect_answers": ["182", "202", "183"]}], [{"question": "Who makes the TIE bomber?", "correct_answer": "Sienar Fleet Systems", "incorrect_answers": ["Corellia Mining Corporation", "Kuat Drive Yards, Imperial Department of Military Research", "Incom Corporation"]}, {"question": "How tall is Leia Organa?", "correct_answer": "150", "incorrect_answers": ["167", "178", "165"]}, {"question": "What is Tatooine's terrain like?", "correct_answer": "desert", "incorrect_answers": ["tundra, ice caves, mountain ranges", "ocean", "gas giant"]}, {"question": "How heavy is Beru Whitesun lars?", "correct_answer": "75", "incorrect_answers": ["32", "77", "84"]}, {"question": "How much does the TIE/LN starfighter cost?", "correct_answer": "unknown", "incorrect_answers": ["14500", "unknown", "unknown"]}], [{"question": "How heavy is R2-D2?", "correct_answer": "32", "incorrect_answers": ["75", "77", "136"]}, {"question": "How much does the Sail barge cost?", "correct_answer": "285000", "incorrect_answers": ["10550", "unknown", "unknown"]}, {"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a TIE/LN starfighter?", "correct_answer": "65", "incorrect_answers": ["1000", "5", "50"]}, {"question": "What is Coruscant's terrain like?", "correct_answer": "cityscape, mountains", "incorrect_answers": ["grasslands, mountains", "tundra, ice caves, mountain ranges", "desert"]}, {"question": "How tall is R5-D4?", "correct_answer": "97", "incorrect_answers": ["96", "178", "165"]}], [{"question": "What is Coruscant's terrain like?", "correct_answer": "cityscape, mountains", "incorrect_answers": ["swamp, jungles", "desert", "jungle, rainforests"]}, {"question": "What episode is A New Hope?", "correct_answer": 4, "incorrect_answers": [3, 1, 6]}, {"question": "Who makes the CR90 corvette?", "correct_answer": "Corellian Engineering Corporation", "incorrect_answers": ["Sienar Fleet Systems, Cyngus Spaceworks", "Sienar Fleet Systems", "Gallofree Yards, Inc."]}, {"question": "When did episode 2 come out?", "correct_answer": "2002-05-16", "incorrect_answers": ["1999-05-19", "2005-05-19", "1983-05-25"]}, {"question": "What's the diameter of Bespin?", "correct_answer": "118000", "incorrect_answers": ["19720", "10200", "12240"]}], [{"question": "What language does a Human speak?", "correct_answer": "Galactic Basic", "incorrect_answers": ["Ewokese", "Mon Calamarian", "Dosh"]}, {"question": "What's the population of Yavin IV?", "correct_answer": "1000", "incorrect_answers": ["6000000", "1000000000000", "30000000"]}, {"question": "Who makes the Death Star?", "correct_answer": "Imperial Department of Military Research, Sienar Fleet Systems", "incorrect_answers": ["Corellian Engineering Corporation", "Sienar Fleet Systems, Cyngus Spaceworks", "Koensayr Manufacturing"]}, {"question": "How much does the X-wing cost?", "correct_answer": "149999", "incorrect_answers": ["150000000", "240000", "100000"]}, {"question": "Who makes the Storm IV Twin-Pod cloud car?", "correct_answer": "Bespin Motors", "incorrect_answers": ["SoroSuub Corporation", "Incom corporation", "Sienar Fleet Systems"]}], [{"question": "What is the average height of a Droid?", "correct_answer": "n/a", "incorrect_answers": ["100", "180", "170"]}, {"question": "When did episode 1 come out?", "correct_answer": "1999-05-19", "incorrect_answers": ["1983-05-25", "2005-05-19", "1980-05-17"]}, {"question": "Who makes the TIE Advanced x1?", "correct_answer": "Sienar Fleet Systems", "incorrect_answers": ["Imperial Department of Military Research, Sienar Fleet Systems", "Kuat Drive Yards, Fondor Shipyards", "Sienar Fleet Systems, Cyngus Spaceworks"]}, {"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a Storm IV Twin-Pod cloud car?", "correct_answer": "10", "incorrect_answers": ["50", "none", "2000000"]}, {"question": "What language does a Rodian speak?", "correct_answer": "Galatic Basic", "incorrect_answers": ["Galactic Basic", "Shyriiwook", "Sullutese"]}], [{"question": "What is the cargo capacity of a X-34 landspeeder?", "correct_answer": "5", "incorrect_answers": ["50000", "2000000", "50"]}, {"question": "What language does a Mon Calamari speak?", "correct_answer": "Mon Calamarian", "incorrect_answers": ["Shyriiwook", "Ewokese", "Sullutese"]}, {"question": "What is Alderaan's terrain like?", "correct_answer": "grasslands, mountains", "incorrect_answers": ["grassy hills, swamps, forests, mountains", "cityscape, mountains", "jungle, rainforests"]}, {"question": "How much does the AT-AT cost?", "correct_answer": "unknown", "incorrect_answers": ["285000", "10550", "14500"]}, {"question": "Who makes the Storm IV Twin-Pod cloud car?", "correct_answer": "Bespin Motors", "incorrect_answers": ["Sienar Fleet Systems", "Kuat Drive Yards, Imperial Department of Military Research", "Ubrikkian Industries Custom Vehicle Division"]}]]